Press play. Subtitles appear.
200+ languages. One app:  tryray.app
Quiet!
Put this on.
Get in.
Hurry!
Kneel!
How have you managed to survive this far.
Second Lieutenant?
Is it the guidance…
Of the God you believe in?
You don't deserve to wear this!
Your sin is unforgivable.
You deserve the death penalty!
But the top brass says
you must be executed in our home country.
You…
Will become an example…
In front of thousands of people.
However.
on my ship.
it is my choice how I treat you.
He is one of the captives
who tried to escape last night.
It's too easy to just kill him.
so we will keep this beast alive.
and make him an example like you.
You will come to realize…
Who your true enemy is.
God…
Has abandoned you.
We're under attack
Multiple targets sighted!
We're under attack.
Man the anti-aircraft guns!
Bring someone immediately.
Torpedo!
Dear God. please forgive me.
Wear this.
It's the same thing.
Have some.
Take this.
Take it.
I'll leave it here.
Saito.
Wait!
Aim here.
Look carefully.
Right here.
It's okay.
Aim here.
Right here.
Now. it's my turn.
Don't worry.
Here we go.
Now you're free.
Look at this.
It's the sea creature we saw.
Move!
Come on. get moving!
Walk faster!
Hurry up. faster!
Hide yourself.
Bring this with you.
Bring it.
Trust me.
Wait. Stop.
I smell something.
Check it out.
Don't shoot!
He's one of us!
Are you okay?
How long have you been here?
Since this morning.
Cigarettes!
Are you from the ship?
Yes.
We survived because we wore life jackets.
Everyone else drowned.
Poor bastards.
Hey!
Hand it over.
Water?
No one else is here?
Just you?
Yes.
Before we were attacked.
there was a rumor…
That a traitor was chained up
with an escapee.
Rumors travel quickly on the ship.
Everyone was making bets…
On who would kill who first.
Hey!
Where is he?
Dead.
Drowned.
And you swam
all the way here with his body?
You…
You're not only a traitor.
but a liar. too.
Where is he?
Orang Ikan…
Orang Ikan!
Hey…
Go…
Bronson. let's go.
Let's go!
Bronson.
No. Let's go.
That.
This way.
It's a mermaid.
A mother.
Bronson. it's not safe here. Let's go!
Wait!
Killing her child
will only make her more vengeful.
Bronson…
My life…
Has carried me to this moment.
Ready. Bronson?
Bronson!
Saito!
Bronson. are you okay?
Bronson!
It's okay.
Look carefully.
Aim here.
Come on!
Who was Bronson?
Was he a prisoner?
Did he help you?
Were you a prisoner?
Were you on that ship?
On the ship carrying prisoners.
What did you do?
I killed my commanding officer.
I couldn't let my comrades die in vain.
so I killed the man who gave that order.
"Bronson"?
Trust me.
Bronson!
He was…
My friend.
Is there anyone else on the island?
There's no one else.
Sailors. we're shippin' off home now.
Full speed ahead.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm